You're the only beat I'll go to
the edge of my
heart If you're
the
only
beat
I'll go to the
edge of my heart I can't see it!
It still doesn't appear.
Open up and head on.
The peroxide moment.
That's just not anything I love The World.
Let me into it.
Take out!
You can't see it!
We'll be there when we go.
We'll be there when we catch up.
Let's keep it in the middle of the world!
Brand New World.
Start me up!
Come on, Luffy.
The suspense is killing me.
Oh, my God.
Okay, she's ready!
We can leave any time!
As soon as Luffy gets here,
we'll set sail immediately!
Sounds good.
Since no one else is saying it, I will.
Right now, there are about as many
battleships out there as there are us.
No matter when we leave,
escaping from this place is
going to be virtually impossible.
This is a report from the
main island front gate.
All personnel of any sloppy have
been collected and accounted for.
We have also identified about 50
pirates as well as a mutinous giant
attempting to escape the island through
the front gate here in the northwest.
It's them!
Sambai and the others,
what did I tell you?
Sounds like they're home free.
No need to worry about that bunch.
Even with thousands of marines
after them, they still won't die.
I'm telling you, this
one time those guys...
We are set with a full
barrage of cannon fire.
They have been eliminated.
All targets are currently presumed dead.
In the island's current conditions,
the chances of survival are impossible.
Repeat, the number of
survivors on any lobby is zero.
This is a report from Battleship Two.
The courthouse and the tower of law located
in the southeast corner of the island?
As well as the underground
passage connecting
the main island to the
bridge of hesitation.
have all been destroyed.
The only remaining target
is the Bridge of Hesitation.
Franky.
They killed all of them.
Good.
You head straight for the courthouse.
The sooner that your crew can
get back together, the better.
That's what I say.
Meanwhile, we'll split into two
groups and bring down the drawbridge.
The Franky family and the
shipwrights from Galley-La.
When you see them, I want you
to pass on a message for me.
You're all fired.
Uymo, Kashi.
You bastards!
How dare you lie to us!
And Yokozuna, I'm sure he
was there right beside them.
So are you up for a fight or what?
Get out!
And what about Sodom and Gomorrah?
They're dead too.
I will follow Big Bro Franky
until the day I die, he says.
That mortar hit him square in the chest.
He's about to go down.
You gotta keep moving no matter what.
You're the only ones who can do this.
He talked about it like it was nothing.
How can they kill people so easily?
I don't think of it that way.
I don't see any people.
To them, it's just a tiny island on a map.
A place they've been sent to erase
from the world without any emotion.
That's what a Buster Call is.
Don't worry, we'll save
you no matter what.
We're all going home together, I promise.
Hurry up, Straw Hat!
Your friends are all here.
They're waiting for you.
Come on!
You hear me?
You better not die, I won't accept it
Franky...
GOM GOM GOM Pistol!!!
He jumped back so the punch
wouldn't hit him as hard!
It's time to end this.
My next attack will push CP9's
killing odds to the limits.
The Sixth Power is extreme!
Secret Technique!
Six King Pistol!
It's like those impact dials
we saw back on Skypiea.
But it feels like these hits
are a heck of a lot harder.
Temperature victory bird!
Goofy!
That luchi guy's strong as hell.
We're lucky we've got
Straw had to hold him back.
I know he could have killed me.
He could probably kill all of
us if he had half a chance.
It's strange, but I
think Luffy always knows.
Right from the start, he can
tell who he has to fight.
Who he has to beat if we're gonna survive.
The pigeon guy's mine!
I'm gonna beat the crap out of him!
He has instincts just like an animal.
Even more than you.
I have a report, sir!
Straw Hat Luffy is in
the first support column.
So he's still alive, then. Listen up.
I want all ships to take position
around the Bridge of Hesitation.
Right away, sir.
He's not gonna die, is he?
Are you stupid?
What'd you say?
You're stupid, stupid!
What now?
The walls are...
The first support column
has now been cut off!
What the hell?
They blew up half the bridge.
Yeah, but why?
Rob Lucci of Cape and Straw Hat Luffy
are both inside the support column.
The battleships are coming this way.
All ships take up combat positions
to run the bridge in hesitation.
On the bridge of the escort ship,
we've identified nine pirates, including
the pirate hunter Zoro and Nico Robin.
We believe that these are the culprits
who defeated Cape in the Tower of Law!
They're coming here to take Robin back.
Well, let them try!
Be careful, everyone.
We shouldn't underestimate the enemy.
Thanks to Cape,
no one has launched a successful attack on
Eni's lobby in its 800 years of history.
Yet this tiny pirate crew wiped them out.
We thought Straw Hat was a rookie,
but as we speak he's going
head-to-head with Rob Lucci,
the strongest fighter Cape has ever seen!
Fighting Lucci and beating
him are two different things.
Right now, their crew is completely
outnumbered and totally surrounded.
We're going to avenge
every defeat we face today!
Look guys, over there!
Hey, Loopy!
We made it!
Everyone got to the bridge safe and sound!
Don't you worry, we're all doing fine!
We even rescued Robin just
like we said we would!
All you gotta do is beat that guy!
We'll be waiting!
I know you can do it!
Don't give up, Loopy!
We're all gonna make it!
We're all going back!
Now it's just a matter of how long we
can hold off all these damn marines.
It seems it's just as you said they
all survived I have to admit I'm rather
impressed But now I'm going to bring
this little rebellion of yours to an
end I will not allow any evil to Prosper
in this world Those ranked lieutenant
commander or below stay put to the
200 elite Captains and commanders,
engage the enemy and wipe
them out immediately!
Captains from headquarters?
All these guys are in the same class
as that smoker guy from before?
There's like a billion of them!
Only thing that proves is
that they're afraid of us.
I'm scared, Granny!
Hold on, where'd Sanji go?
He was here just a second ago. Damn it.
The one time I want that stupid
cook around and he runs away.
All hands prepare to move in.
Let's go!
Stop trying to show off,
just attack already.
Now this should be fun.
I could always use some
more heads to bust.
No matter what happens, we
can't give them an inch.
Until Luffy makes it here,
we have to hold our ground.
We need to get down to the bridge.
If they damage this ship, we can't escape.
I won't let them capture me ever again.
Darn it!
I can't move!
Destroy them! Yeah!
Capture Nico Robin and bring her here!
We're not giving her back after
all the trouble we've gone through.
You can send me as many
captains as you want.
Let's do this.
You can send in my share of captains too!
Weapons left.
Let's go!
Beating one at a time is too much trouble.
I'll take you all on at once!
Bear witness to the
power of the Sniper King!
The Blaster!
You want to fight with guns?
I can do that!
Damn pirate!
You ready?
What's left? Take this!
You want some more?
How about a strong run?
Uh-oh!
The bad guys are coming, Granny!
Well, that ain't good.
You stay here and guard the boat, Robin.
I'll do my best to hold them back.
Here I come!
Now thunder, charge!
Swing arm!
Thunderball!
The hell? The clouds!
Oh, that one's my thunderbolt tempo.
I did it!
She's mocking us with
that ridiculous weapon!
Lambs of respect, pirate!
Robin!
You don't have to worry
about protecting me anymore.
If the crew is fighting,
then I'm fighting, too.
There's more?
Nothing to see here, boys!
We're just hostages!
Don't find us!
Luke, you'll be here soon.
We can't give up.
What's the matter?
Don't tell me that blood pumping technique
of yours is losing its head already.
It's pointless to struggle.
You never stood a chance against the
world government in the first place.
Face the facts!
Don't come!
Shut up!
I don't care if this island
is burned to the ground.
So long as that woman is
wanted by the world government,
I'll chase her to the ends
of the earth if need be.
That is the meaning of God's justice!
You won't be chasing anyone!
Come on, I'm putting an end
to this right here, right now!
Shit!
Six king guns!
I don't know.
Oh, no!
I got him! Watch out!
Chairman, there's no time for
you to be spacing out, Uso!
Luffy!
What the hell are you doing?
Get up!
Luffy!
Weapons left!
Super!
Commander!
No Straw Hats or no ordinary pirates!
They're insanely strong!
They're holding their
own against the captains!
Huh, so that woman has Devil Fruit powers.
Everyone attack on my command, go!
Now see and close.
With a flip.
Here we go. Thunderbolts!
Thunderbolts!
That'll teach you to mess with us!
Guess these guys are a bit
stronger than your average Marine.
Two-sword style.
Who wants their ass kicked next?
Usopp.
Lupin!
Can you hear me?
Usa, I didn't know you were here, too.
Don't get the wrong idea!
I just came here to save
Robin, that's it, all right?
I didn't come to see you or
your stupid face, understand me?
Come on, enough!
I'm an idiot!
Hey, you!
The Cape boss can't!
I know you hear me!
From here on out, I'm your opponent!
Come and get some!
Yeah, that's right!
If you mess with Robin,
then you mess with me!
Wait, hey!
Get back here!
You leave him alone!
This is between you and me!
You've already lost.
I have no business with you.
I'm going to kill every last one
of them and save you for last.
You can watch it happen.
Come get me, boss kitty cat!
I am going to take you out!
You idiot!
Shut up already!
He's going to kill you!
You shut up!
What the hell are you
going to do about it, Hoff?
You're almost dead!
That pigeon bastard's mine, I'm gonna kick
his ass all over the place! Hey, get up!
Show him what you're made of!
Stop lying around comfy and
bleeding like you're about to die!
That is not the loopy I know at all!
Even though it's filled with
smoke, we can still see the sky!
We can still see the ocean!
This place isn't hell!
I can't believe you'd
let it end like this!
So stop acting like you're about
to die, you stupid bastard!
What's wrong with you?
Why are you trying to make us worry?
GET UP AND FIGHT!
You're right, Usa.
This place is in hell.
It's not even close.
Luffy.
Finish him!
Then we can all leave this place together!
I'll win no matter what!
I'm surprised you can stand.
I'm never gonna give up.
You hear me?
Until I defeat you,
I won't drop to the ground ever again.
Again now life return terminate this
annoying farce of yours has gone on long
enough i'll crush you with a single blow
and end this once and for all oh and don't
worry about your little friends just as
you wished you all be reunited once again
very soon once i kill you there next Then
you'll spend eternity together in hell.
Bloods attack!
Luffy!
Victory burn!
Ah!
Damn it!
What's up with these guys?
I can't hit any of them!
Hey!
I got him!
That's the power of the berry berry fruit.
Dude, it's buried, dead.
Damn it all, I can't even move here.
You're finished.
Hey, thanks.
Oh, wait, just where do
you think you're going?
If you like flying around so much.
No, don't, hold on a sec.
Then weapons left.
Be careful!
Some of these jerks
have Devil Fruit powers!
They could say the same of me.
It's time for train de flu.
And clutch!
You must be Roro Noah Zoro.
That's right.
What's it to you?
I'm here to eliminate you!
Good luck with that.
I ate the rust rust fruit
and became a rust man.
You and your swords will never defeat me.
Damn it, my Ubershiri.
That was just the beginning.
I'll turn all your blades
into little piles of rust.
That's an interesting trick.
But it won't work twice.
By the way, if you think that's all
I can do, you're sadly mistaken!
No! What happened? What can I move?
Because I rusted every
single joint in your body.
Now let's gather rest of you as well.
Damn it!
Firebird star!
Are you all right, swordsman?
Come, come, jet pistol!
Now come, come, jet pistol!
I won't fall for that one again!
Ultimate radius, six king gun!
Until I defeat you,
I won't drop to the ground ever again!
Keep a close eye on Nicole
Robin she'll grow to be
more than you can handle now
Gum-Gum no it's over this
is the last time you'll see
me this is world government
business people like you
should and stay out of it.
She did it all for us, you know!
She's going to sacrifice herself!
What is funny?
You're all going to die!
You morons can't challenge the
entire world and expect to win!
So long as that woman is wanted by the
world government, I'll chase her forever.
I want to live!
Oh, my God!
What happened?
What the heck's going on over there?
Luffy!
Whoa, look at the tower!
Hey, wait, what is that?
Down there, you see?
Attention aboard all ships!
I have an urgent report!
Just now, Rob Lucci,
the most powerful agent of CP9,
was seen lying face down at a
lifeless in the first column.
I repeat, Rob Lucci has just
been defeated by Straw Hat Luffy!
It's over.
We should be okay now.
We're all going back together!
Robin!
Oh, my God.